# **Backend Developer**

Phan Quốc Hùng

0797720574

O District 8, Ho Chi Minh City

Github: https://github.com/PhanHunggg

https://portfolio-mocha-seven-50.vercel.app/

# **MOTTO**

I'm a Software Developer. I have experience in JavaScript/Typescript, Nestjs, JWT, Bcrypt, MySQL, and MongoDB. Strong teamwork skills, a passion for learning, and a focus on innovation. At the same time, I want to improve and become a full-stack developer.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Geek up

June 2024 - August 2024

# PRODUCT BACKEND INTERN

- I used Agile Scrum during my internship at Geek Up, tracking progress through sprints and daily stand-ups.
- I collaborated with product design and analysis teams.
- I worked with TypeORM, PostgreSQL, and NestJS for database and API management.
- I deployed with Nginx and Docker to enhance speed, and scalability, and streamline the CI/CD process.
- I aim to integrate Grafana for logging and monitoring to analyze server metrics.

# CyberSoft Academy

Feb 2023 - May 2023

### **BACKEND INTERN**

- Gained hands-on experience through projects, coding, and problem-solving in a team environment
- Focused on building back-end services using NodeJS, NestJS, and Prisma.

# **PROJECTS**

### **Project 1: Ecommerce**

February 25, 2024 -May 20, 2024

Team size: 1

Webservice:

https://github.com/PhanHunggg/ /E-commerce.git

## YOUR POSITION IN PROJECT

- Build commercial web services. Can sell a wide range of things, including clothes, phones, and shoes...vv.
- Build an API with an API key, access token, and refresh token, use software design patterns, decentralize permissions, and manage problems.
- Users can register, log in, add to the cart, change the amount of things in the cart, and view more items.

### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

Nodejs, MongoDB, Mongoose, JWT, Bcrypt,...

### **Project 2: Store phone**

Late November - Mid February 2023

Team size: 1

Webservice: https://phone-

be.onrender.com/swagger

### YOUR POSITION IN PROJECT

- Build a web service for the Phone Store. Can sell a variety of phones and iPads.
- Users receive an email confirming their registration, which grants them access once verified. Unconfirmed users are reminded to confirm. Password resets result in a forgotten password email, which allows users to change their password using a link on the website.

· Secure user credentials and provide a personalized experience with a strong

**TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION** authentication system based on JWTs and Bcrypt.

Nestjs, Prisma, JWT, MySQL, Nodemailer, Bcrypt...

# **Project 3: Fiver clone**

August 2023 - October 2023

Team size: 1

Webservice:

https://fiver-sever.vercel.app/

## YOUR POSITION IN PROJECT

- Build a web service clone of Fiverr that includes APIs for authentication, job type, job type details, job category, work, and job hire.
- · Build a full basic API that meets CRUD.
- Secure user credentials and provide a personalized experience with a strong authentication system based on JWTs and Bcrypt.

### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

TypeScript, Prisma, MySQL, NestJS, Bcrypt,...

# Project 4: API Service Book movie tickets

March 31, 2023 - April 12, 2023

Team size 1

Git:

https://github.com/PhanHunggg /NestJs\_Movie.git

## YOUR POSITION IN PROJECT

- APIs can add, delete, edit, and update movies, users, seats, showtimes, and ticketing.
- Secure user credentials and provide a personalized experience with a strong authentication system based on JWTs and Bcrypt.
- At the same time, it displays all booked and unbooked tickets, and normal and VIP seats.

### **TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION**

TypeScript, Prisma, MySQL, NestJS, Bcrypt,...

# SKILLS

# **Programming Languages:**

Java (Basic), JavaScript, TypeScript.

### Frameworks / Platforms/RDBMS:

HTML, CSS, ReactJS, NodeJS, NestJS, Prisma, TypeORM, MySQL, MongoDB, Monitoring, Grafana, Docker, PostgreSQL.

### Foreign Languages:

English (reading).

## Soft Skills:

Teamwork, Technical communication, Highly adaptable.

# EDUCATION

2021 - 2024

## **SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGY**

Gia Dinh University

# INTEREST

I enjoy engaging in team-building activities, reading technology books, watching movies, and talking with others about life and work concerns.

# ORTHER

Organization and time management, self-discipline and responsibility, and willingness to learn new skills.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

### 2023